<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Clifton Park Real Estate Podcast with Willie Miranda</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Miranda Real Estate Group - your professional Clifton Park Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Willie Miranda</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2020-10-14 12:36:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Willie Miranda</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>wmiranda@mrgteam.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Willie Miranda</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Clifton Park Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Miranda Real Estate Group - your professional Clifton Park Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Why Do I Need a Notepad for Listing Appointments?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-do-i-need-a-notepad-for-listing-appointments.html</link>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-28 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/Why+Do+I+Need+a+Notepad+for+Listing+Appointments.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s why you should always bring a notepad to listing appointments.

Today I want to impart the value of using a tool most real estate agents don’t even think about when going on listing appointments. It’s very simple: a notepad.

I’ve been bringing a notepad to listing appointments for the past 15 years because early on, I learned the reason that I needed it the hard way. Years ago I lost a couple of listings, and when I called to follow up with them, the seller said they felt I didn’t seem very interested in the property. One client said that the agent they chose brought a notepad, a pen, and took notes on the updates we made to our home. When I walked through their house I was taking mental notes, but they couldn’t see that.

So since that day, I’ve always brought a notepad to listing appointments. This is my advice to you: Take physical notes on any improvements the client has made to their property. Also, take either mental or physical notes about anything negative you notice about the home, then compliment them on the good things, whether it’s a great lot, beautiful landscaping, attractive kitchen tile, etc.

Make sure you don’t say things such as, “Who picked out the paint color in this room?” or “Wow, you’ll have to replace these carpets.” That’s no way to build a rapport in the first 15 minutes of meeting someone. Sellers are frequently emotional about their house, so they’re apprehensive and will take offense to unfavorable comments. Following this advice will help you win more listings.

“Take physical notes about any improvements the client has made to their property.”

If you have questions about listing appointments or real estate in general, call or leave a comment below. I would love to help you. Let’s go get ‘em this week!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/Why+Do+I+Need+a+Notepad+for+Listing+Appointments.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/Why+Do+I+Need+a+Notepad+for+Listing+Appointments.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s why you should always bring a notepad to listing appointments.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s why you should always bring a notepad to listing appointments.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Stand Out in a Listing Appointment?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-stand-out-in-a-listing-appointment.html</link>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2020-09-14 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/How+Can+You+Stand+Out+in+a+Listing+Appointment_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Our pre-listing packet sets us apart from other listing agents.

Do you have a pre-listing packet for your listing appointments? How do you stand out in these important meetings? Today I’m going to explain each of the 10 different items we send out prior to a listing appointment to help our agents stand out among the competition. Each one of the 10 items we include in our pre-listing packet is there for a reason, and you’ll learn about all of them today.

Cited below for your convenience are timestamps that will direct you to the 10 different items discussed in the video. Feel free to watch it in its entirety, or use these timestamps to browse information about specific items at your leisure:

1:13 — No. 1: A customized blue box or folder

1:50 — No. 2: A home seller’s guide

2:42 — No. 3: A “Meet the Team” booklet

3:47 — No. 4: Your biography

4:16 — No. 5: Testimonials from past clients

4:56 — No. 6: A seller book

5:46 — No. 7: A personal brochure

6:25 — No. 8: A business card

6:35 — No. 9: Your marketing plan

7:04 — No. 10: A screenshot of online reviews

7:35 — Bonus tip

8:12 — Wrapping things up

If you have questions for me about pre-listing packets or anything else related to the real estate business, don’t hesitate to reach out via phone or email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/How+Can+You+Stand+Out+in+a+Listing+Appointment_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/How+Can+You+Stand+Out+in+a+Listing+Appointment_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Our pre-listing packet sets us apart from other listing agents.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Our pre-listing packet sets us apart from other listing agents.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>5 Things I Wish I Knew Before Starting My Real Estate Career</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/5-things-i-wish-i-knew-before-starting-my-real-estate-career.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2020-08-17 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/5+Things+I+Wish+I+Knew+Before+Starting+My+Real+Estate+Career.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here are the five things I wish I&rsquo;d known before diving into real estate.

Knowledge can be gained by anyone at any moment, but only time and experience can yield wisdom. When I look back on my career in real estate, there are five things in particular that I wish I’d known before jumping into the business. Most of these lessons I learned the hard way, but I’m sharing them in the hope that aspiring new agents can be spared the trial and error, and hit the ground running.

1. Building a database. I never knew how important it was to not only build a list of contacts but also regularly engage with those people. Today, we have an 18-step follow-up process so that our database receives something from us every month. As my database has grown over the years, so has my business.

2. Buying more leads. Whether you’re buying them on Zillow, Realtor.com, or UpNest, it’s so easy to buy leads these days. If you have the proper follow-up and have the right systems in place, those leads you buy today turn into business tomorrow and referrals after that. Buying leads allowed me to grow my database by bringing in new clientele while I strengthened the relationships I had already established.

3. The importance of follow-ups.  You’ve probably heard the saying, “The fortune’s in the follow-up,” and that couldn’t be more true; 80% of sales are made on the fifth to twelfth contact. I didn’t have those expectations at first, so I treated a lot of the leads from cold calling, open houses, or online like referrals. I’d call them once or twice, and if I didn’t hear back, well, I just figured they weren’t interested. Making sure you have a system in place to consistently follow-up on leads is so important.

4. Having a business plan. Goals written down stand a better chance of becoming reality. I always tried to exceed what I did last year, but sitting down with a coach and projecting three, five, or even 10 years out (which can be hard to do) was so game-changing for me. It allowed me to wake up every day and know I was moving in a positive and specific direction. Make sure you have someone who holds you accountable to your business plan and encourages you so that you reach the next level.

5. Employee versus entrepreneur mindset. We real estate agents are 1099 contractors—entrepreneurs at the helm of our own business. Coming into this business, however, I brought an employee mindset; many people would say to me, “The sky’s the limit, you can make as much as you want,” but what they never told me is that there’s no floor in real estate. If I were to do it all over again, I would’ve taken more time at the start to learn about entrepreneurship and what other successful business owners have done. I ultimately implemented a lot of great practices I learned directly from industry leaders and observed elsewhere.

“The fortune’s in the follow-up.”

If you have any questions about this business or some of the tools, techniques, and systems that have made all the difference in my business, don’t hesitate to reach out to me via phone or email. I’d be more than happy to chat with you!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/5+Things+I+Wish+I+Knew+Before+Starting+My+Real+Estate+Career.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/5+Things+I+Wish+I+Knew+Before+Starting+My+Real+Estate+Career.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here are the five things I wish I’d known before diving into real estate.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here are the five things I wish I’d known before diving into real estate.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Give Your Database a Boost?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-give-your-database-a-boost.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-19 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/How+Can+You+Give+Your+Database+a+Boost_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Here&rsquo;s why agents&rsquo; success is dependent on the growth of their databases.

Just the other day, I was talking to an agent who has been in the business for more than 16 years and sold hundreds of homes. She mentioned seeing a decline in her activity over the past couple of years, especially in her repeat and referral business.

I asked what she uses for a CRM, and she said she didn’t have one. She admitted that, for one reason or another, all of her files are stored in a big cabinet down in her basement. “How are you communicating with your past clients?” I asked. She keeps some contacts on her phone and interacts with others via real estate. Others still just know to call her if they need real estate. That’s how she’s been operating for the past several years.

This is what I told her: My dentist sold his own business not too long ago, and it wasn’t his equipment or the fancy chair he had out in the lobby that made the sale possible. It was the relationship he had with his database. In real estate, your success or failure is directly tied to your database. If your database is small and stagnant, your business will stay small and ultimately stagnate. However, when you start making efforts to grow your database, you’re bound to become more successful.

I gave her a few tips on how she can grow her database, and the first one was obvious: 

1. Get a CRM. You can get a free CRM at hubspot.com. Their software is great and has an easy-to-use interface for your computer, tablet device, or phone. You can keep tabs on all of your contacts and mark follow-ups as needed.

2. Add five files every day. Instead of tackling years of accrued files at one time, I recommended she just start small. For each file, list their name, number, email, and address. Reach out to them and let them know the market is doing really well right now; ask them, “Are you looking to make a move in 2020?” Whatever their answer is, document it on their file. Five files a day times five days a week equals 25 contacts. In four weeks, you’ll have more than 100 contacts. Once you reach 300 contacts, and correspond with them via market update videos, your business will start booming.

“If your database is small and stagnant, your business will stay small and ultimately stagnate.”

As always, reach out to me via phone or email if you have questions about this or any other real estate-related topic. I look forward to hearing from you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/How+Can+You+Give+Your+Database+a+Boost_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/2020/How+Can+You+Give+Your+Database+a+Boost_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Here’s why agents’ success is dependent on the growth of their databases.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Here’s why agents’ success is dependent on the growth of their databases.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can I Get My Goals Back on Track?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-i-get-my-goals-back-on-track.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2020-07-08 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/Recruiting/2020/How+Can+I+Get+My+Goals+Back+on+Track_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

These three steps will ensure you achieve your goals for 2020.

First, I’d like to say congratulations for making it through the first half of 2020; there were many bumps in the road. If you’re a bit off track for reaching your goals this year, I’m sharing the three steps for how to get back on pace to achieve them:

1. Make a goal. You need a clear, written goal; you can make a new one, or revise the ones you made in January. This goal could be to make more calls, reach out to your database more, develop a farm, create more videos, be more active on social media, etc.

2. Make a plan. How many days per week will you work on this goal? What vacation time are you taking? What will it take, and what plans are you putting in place to reach your goal? Think through everything to ensure your plan can get you to your goal this year.

3. Take action. This is the most critical step. You need to carry out the tasks necessary to achieve your goal. By changing a few activities daily, in just a few weeks you’ll begin to see progress.

“You need a clear, written goal.”

I wish you the best in 2020. Don’t give up; even if you’re a little behind on your goals, don’t lower them.

If you have questions about these steps or concerning real estate in general, please reach out via phone or email. I would be glad to help you.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/Recruiting/2020/How+Can+I+Get+My+Goals+Back+on+Track_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Willie+Miranda/Recruiting/2020/How+Can+I+Get+My+Goals+Back+on+Track_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>These three steps will ensure you achieve your goals for 2020.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>These three steps will ensure you achieve your goals for 2020.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Invest in Yourself</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/invest-in-yourself.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2020-02-28 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

How do you stay on top of your priorities and keep your head from exploding? I’ll share three ways to assure you get the most out of your day, every day.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>How do you stay on top of your priorities and keep your head from exploding?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>How do you stay on top of your priorities and keep your head from exploding?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>4 Lead Generation Tips every Real Estate Agent Should be Using</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/4-lead-generation-tips-every-real-estate-agent-should-be-using.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2019-06-15 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Has lead generation been a challenge for you this year?

I recently spoke to a group of great agents in Florida that had some of the same challenges. Here are the four lead generation tips I shared with them:


  Database
  Social Media
  Open Houses
  Geographic Farming


These four simple activities are easy to implement and will generate tons of leads for you in your business!


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Has lead generation been a challenge for you this year?</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Has lead generation been a challenge for you this year?</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Best Daily Lead Generation Tip</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/best-daily-lead-generation-tip.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2019-02-24 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

I recently received a question asking “What is the best lead generation strategy?” Here’s my answer.


  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I recently received a question asking "What is the best lead generation strategy?" Here's my answer.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I recently received a question asking "What is the best lead generation strategy?" Here's my answer.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Interviewing Million Dollar Listing's Ryan Serhant</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/interviewing-million-dollar-listings-ryan-serhant.html</link>
        
          <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <author>Willie Miranda</author>
        <pubDate>2018-12-14 18:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

Check out what Ryan Serhant has to say about the future of social media and the strategies for getting ahead in the real estate market.

Willie and his brother, Brian Miranda (General Manager/Associate Broker at Miranda Real Estate Group, Inc.), travel to NYC for the day to meet with Ryan Serhant, the star of Million Dollar Listing New York, and the author of “Sell It Like Serhant.”

Check out what Ryan has to say about the future of social media and the strategies for getting ahead in the real estate market.

Some of today’s takeaways include:


  There are a lot of things you cannot control, but how hard you work isn’t one of them. 
  Why “Personal Branding” is essential today to be successful in business.
  Everything you do is a choice.
  The person that cares the least holds the power.



  

</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Check out what Ryan Serhant has to say about the future of social media and the strategies for getting ahead in the real estate market.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Willie Miranda</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Check out what Ryan Serhant has to say about the future of social media and the strategies for getting ahead in the real estate market.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Clifton Park, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Willie Miranda</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Willie Miranda</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Miranda Real Estate Group - your professional Clifton Park Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
